现在轮到你来建立气温单位的设定。这
Now its your turn to build the temperature unit setting. This
将会联合很多你已经学过的概念，而且需要
will bring together a lot of the concepts that you've learned and
花一些时间生效，但是我们觉得你已经准备好了。
will take some time to implement, but we think you're ready for
修正程序，这样正确的气温单位将展示
it. Modify the app, so that the right temperature units are displayed
给用户。假设我们在同步公制数据从
to the user. Use the assumption that we're syncing metric data from
服务器中。最终，我们将在设备上拥有一个服务器，而且我们
the server. Eventually, we'll have a database on the device and we
并不希望这里有华氏和摄氏的温度。因此
don't want a mix of Fahrenheit and Celsius data in there. Hence,
我们会通过从服务器获取公制数据来保持一致。然后
we'll stay consistent by getting metric data from the server. And then,
我们会联机转换到偏好的单位在
we'll convert on the fly to the preferred units when
我们更新用户界面的时候。在你修改完这些后，我会展示
we update the UI. After you make these changes, I'll show
给你看这在设备上是什么样的。如果你
you what it looks like on the device. If you
进入设置，你可以看到温度单位选项。如果你
go to settings, you'll see the temperature units preference. If you
点击它，你可以看见有两个选项的对话框
tap on that, you see a dialog with two options.
如果你转换到英制，然后返回到
If you switch to imperial and then you go back to
预报列表，你会看见现在所有的气温
the forecast list, then you see that all the temperatures now
都用华氏表示。当这件事成功后，回答这个问题。那个子类
are in Fahrenheit. Once it works, answer this question. Which subclass
是你刚刚用过的？
of preference did you use?